Inventory of the Papers of Judge John W. Bissell, 1983-2005
University of Virginia, Arthur J. Morris Law Library
- Papers, 1997 (Box 51-54)
  - Eubank v. Portside Apartments Urban Renewal Co. 1997 April 09 (Box 52)
    Opinion; Order; Opinion; Order (1997 November 12); Opinion; Order (1997 August 14)
  - Fallon v. Marxen 1997 July 24 (Box 52)
  - Fed. Deposit Ins. Corp. v. Garidis 1997 March 25 (Box 52)
  - Feidt v. Owens Corning Fiberglass 1997 January 06 (Box 52)
  - In re Ford Motor Co. Ignition Switch Prod. Liab. Litig. 1997 September 30 (Box 52)
    Opinion; Order [Simandle, J.]
  - Fraternal Order of Police v. City of Newark 1997 July 29 (Box 52)
    Opinion; Exhibit A; Exhibit B
  - Gallo v. Reich 1997 October 20 (Box 52)
  - Estate of Gibbs v. United States 1997 August 12 (Box 52)
    Opinion; Decision-Order (1997 October 29)
    Estate of Gibbs v. United States, No. 96-685, 1997 U.S. Dist. LEXIS 23359 (D. N.J. Aug. 12, 1997).
  - Hallas v. Kral 1997 September 16 (Box 52)
  - Harris v. County of Hudson 1997 August 12 (Box 52)
  - Hawkins v. Mobilemedia 1997 March 31 (Box 52)
  - Holquin v. United States 1997 April 07 (Box 52)
  - Hook v. Transaction Publishers 1997 March 17 (Box 52)
  - In re Hudson Gate II Apartments Corp. 1997 June 23 (Box 52)
  - Int'l Longshoremen's Ass'n Local 1478-2 v. Pittston Warehouse Corp. 1997 April 24 (Box 52)
  - Interstate Consol. Serv. v. Team Express 1997 January 08 (Box 52)
  - J.I. Hass Co. v. Gilbane Bldg. Co. 1997 January 08 (Box 52)
  - Joyce v. RJR Nabisco Holdings Corp. 1997 December 23 (Box 52)
  - Kennedy Funding v. Upland Dev. 1997 July 24 (Box 52)
  - KIA Heavy Indus. Corp. v. Contempo Design 1997 August 14 (Box 52)
  - Knight v. Lewis 1997 November 14 (Box 52)
  - L.R. v. N. Plainfield Bd. of Ed. 1997 September 15 (Box 52)
    Opinion; Order; Opinion; Order (1997 November 07)
  - Larry Tucker, Inc. v. Husky Envelope Prod. 1997 July 22 (Box 52)
  - Lebel Realty v. Twp. of Mahwah 1997 August 07 (Box 52)
  - Leonard Studio Equip. v. Desmar Corp. 1997 July 10 (Box 52)
    Opinion; Order; Appendix A
  - Lexington Ins. v. Diamond State Ins. Co. 1997 October 16 (Box 52)
  - Linnen v. Kerness 1997 January 17 (Box 52)
  - Little v. G.E. Capital Mortgage Serv. 1997 July 22 (Box 52)
  - Loftiss v. Borough of Palisades Park 1997 June 04 (Box 53)
    Opinion; Order; Order Amending Order
  - Louis v. City of East Orange 1997 September 23 (Box 53)
    Opinion; Order; Opinion (1997 October 16); Order
  - Mackerley v. Percudani 1997 September 19 (Box 53)
  - Mainenti v. Servicemaster Co. 1997 January 06 (Box 53)
  - Mainenti v. Sukennikoff 1997 February 20 (Box 53)
  - Mansol Assoc. v. Mansol Indus. 1997 August 21 (Box 53)
  - Martin v. Comm'r 1997 November 03 (Box 53)
  - Mazzei v. Liberty-Kenworth-Hino Truck Sales 1997 August 12 (Box 53)
  - Mercedes v. Morton 1997 April 07 (Box 53)
  - Mette v. Egles 1997 November 07 (Box 53)
    Opinion; Order to proceed in forma pauperis (1997 November 06)
  - Metzler v. Westinghouse Elec. Corp. 1997 May 07 (Box 53)
  - Miwon Am. v. Ex-Im Plastics 1997 January 07 (Box 53)
    Korea
  - Murphy v. Enesco Corp. 1997 October 21 (Box 53)
  - N.J. Psychological Ass'n v. MCC Behavioral Care 1997 September 15 (Box 53)
    N.J. Psychological Ass'n v. MCC Behavioral Care, No. 96-3080, 1997 U.S. Dist. LEXIS 16338 (D. N.J. Sept. 15, 1997).
  - Noire v. Givaudan-Roure Corp. 1997 September 18 (Box 53)
  - Noorily v. Thomas & Betts Co. 1997 June 04 (Box 53)
  - Obiukwu v. State 1997 November 10 (Box 53)
  - Ohrid v. Megasafe Indus. 1997 May 09 (Box 53)
    Yugoslavia
  - Old Bridge Owners Coop. Corp. v. Twp. of Old Bridge 1997 March 13 (Box 53)
    Letter-Opinion; Exhibit A; Opinion; Order (1997 July 31); Opinion; Order (1997 October 29)
    Old Bridge Owners Coop. Corp. v. Twp. of Old Bridge, 981 F. Supp. 884 (D. N.J. 1997).
  - O'Neill v. Allmerica Inst. Serv. 1997 January 16 (Box 53)
  - Ortiz v. Baker & Taylor 1997 May 08 (Box 53)
  - Ortiz v. Comm'r 1997 August 04 (Box 53)
  - Paramount Aviation Corp. v. Agusta 1997 April 04 (Box 53)
  - Phone Express v. Pub. Switch Corp. 1997 July 31 (Box 53)
    New Hampsire
  - Polk v. Dobbs Int'l Serv. 1997 February 24 (Box 53)
  - Pray v. United States 1997 December 09 (Box 54)
    Georgia
  - Ribeiro v. DelColle 1997 December 18 (Box 54)
  - Roland v. Comm'r 1997 December 15 (Box 54)
  - Santana v. Comm'r 1997 November 19 (Box 54)
  - Sarullo v. U.S. Postal Serv. 1997 December 18 (Box 54)
  - Schneider & Marquard v. Nanticoke Micro Tech. 1997 January 30 (Box 54)
  - Seeward v. Frieder 1997 September 15 (Box 54)
  - Seibert v. Nusbaum, Stein, Goldstein, Bronstein & Compeau 1997 August 20 (Box 54)
    Opinion; Order; Opinion; Order (1997 December 31)
  - Shamsid-Deen v. Twp. of Scotch Plains 1997 August 01 (Box 54)
  - Shamsid-Din v. Arvonio 1997 January 07 (Box 54)
  - Sightyet Inv. v. Golden Line Freight Forwarder Co. 1997 August 11 (Box 54)
  - Slapikas v. Cerasia 1997 February 26 (Box 54)
    Opinion; Order; Order Awarding Attorneys' Fees, Expenses, Etc. (1997 April 25)
  - Sook Son v. State Farm Ins. Co. 1997 July 24 (Box 54)
    Opinion; Order; Order Amending Opinion and Order (1997 August 07)
  - Starbare III Partners v. Richardson 1997 November 14 (Box 54)
    Opinion; Order; Opinion; Order (1997 December 31); Exhibit A
  - Status Int'l v. M & D Mar. 1997 November 20 (Box 54)
    Farmland
    Morocco
    Pakistan
  - Stone Container Corp. v. Int'l Bhd. of Teamsters, Local 560 1997 October 08 (Box 54)
  - Storm v. Young 1997 August 20 (Box 54)
  - Stretch Devices v. Charles M. Jessup, Inc. 1997 January 03 (Box 54)
  - Swint v. Fed. Parole Bd. 1997 October 30 (Box 54)
  - Tarrabocchia v. Comm'r 1997 August 04 (Box 54)
  - Terrafranca v. Virgin Atl. Airways 1997 January 17 (Box 54)
    Terrorism
    England
    Terrafranca v. Virgin Atl. Airways, No. 96-976, 1997 U.S. Dist. LEXIS 3259 (D. N.J. Jan. 17, 1997).
  - Thomas v. United States 1997 August 18 (Box 54)
  - Thompson v. Corestates Fin. Corp. 1997 December 08 (Box 54)
  - True v. Hakin 1997 October 28 (Box 54)
  - United States v. Miles 1997 March 26 (Box 54)
  - Vacca v. Grover 1997 November 06 (Box 54)
  - Wakefield v. Fauver 1997 April 10 (Box 54)
  - Worsley v. U.S. Marshal Serv. 1997 April 17 (Box 54)
  - Zenith Lab. v. Abbott Lab. 1997 October 01 (Box 54)
    Zenith Lab. v. Abbott Lab., No. 96-1661, 1997 U.S. Dist. LEXIS 23954 (D. N.J. Oct. 1, 1997).
- Papers, 1998 (Box 55-59)
  All papers dated 1998.
  - Abdul-Aliim v. State 1998 February 12 (Box 55)
  - Advanced Web Creations v. Apex Global Internet Serv. 1998 October 06 (Box 55)
  - Alvarez v. Dep't of Corr. 1998 April 17 (Box 55)
  - Amalgamated Transit Union Local No. 1541 v. Ace Bus Transp. Corp. 1998 July 06 (Box 55)
    Opinion; Order [incorrectly titled "Opinion"]; Opinion; Order (1998 September 04)
  - Balisnomo v. Pinchak 1998 April 16 (Box 55)
  - Boguslavsky v. Hosman 1998 January 13 (Box 55)
    Opinion; Order Ι Opinion; Order (1997 August 17)
  - Bostic v. N.J. Ins. Underwriting Ass'n 1998 August 31 (Box 55)
  - Bravo v. Appel 1998 August 04 (Box 55)
  - Brennan v. Novartis Pharm. 1998 November 04 (Box 55)
  - Brown v. United States 1998 July 06 (Box 55)
  - Bryant v. Morton 1998 August 07 (Box 55)
    Opinion; Order Ι Opinion; Order (1998 March 30)
  - Carvajal v. Lewis 1998 March 25 (Box 55)
  - C.M. v. Bd. of Ed. of Union County 1998 November 10 (Box 55)
  - Colwell v. Gemini Consulting 1998 October 30 (Box 55)
  - Cosmetic Group v. Zegarelli Group Int'l 1998 August 05 (Box 55)
    Opinion; Order Ι Opinion; Order (1998 November 30)
  - Crowley v. Anheuser-Busch 1998 January 27 (Box 55)
    Opinon; Order
  - Daewoo Int'l v. Sea-Land Orient 1998 May 27 (Box 55)
    Daewoo Int'l v. Sea-Land Orient, 32 F. Supp. 2d 705 (D. N.J. 1998).
  - Dainoski v. Witco Corp. 1998 April 22 (Box 55)
  - Danka Funding Co. v. Mitchell Co. 1998 June 04 (Box 55)
    Opinion; Order Ι Opinon; Order (1997 December 15)
  - Delbono v. County of Middlesex 1998 January 12 (Box 55)
    Opinion; Order Ι Order (1998 October 13)
  - DeMaria v. Home Depot 1998 March 30 (Box 55)
    DeMaria v. Home Depot, No. 97-5987, 1998 U.S. Dist. LEXIS 23070 (D. N.J. Mar. 30, 1998).
  - Diaz v. Comm'r 1998 July 06 (Box 55)
  - Disla v. Comm'r 1998 August 13 (Box 55)
  - Du v. Hibernia Post Office 1998 February 17 (Box 55)
  - Eubank v. Portside Apartments Urban Renewal Co. 1998 January 28 (Box 55)
    Opinion; Order Ι Opinion; Order (1998 August 28) Ι Opinion; Order (1998 August 31)
  - Falconieri v. Eden 1998 August 06 (Box 55)
  - Farrow v. Chrysler Corp. 1998 May 20 (Box 56)
  - Frazier Indus. Co. v. Eastcore 1998 July 07 (Box 56)
  - Garcia v. Comm'r 1998 April 17 (Box 56)
  - Estate of Gibbs v. United States 1998 January 13 (Box 56)
    Transfer and inheritance taxes
    Estate of Gibbs v. United States, No. 96-685, 1998 U.S. Dist. LEXIS 1312 (D. N.J. Jan. 12, 1998).
  - Gilmore v. Pinchak 1998 October 02 (Box 56)
  - Gomar Mfg. Co. v. Novelli 1998 January 28 (Box 56)
    Opinion; Order; Opinion; Order (1998 March 24); Opinion; Order (1998 April 13)
    Computer crimes and identity theft
    Broadcasting, cable, digital technologies
    Gomar Mfg. Co. v. Novelli, No. 96-4000, 1998 U.S. Dist. LEXIS 23452 (D. N.J. Apr. 13, 1998).; No. 96-4000, 1998 U.S. Dist. LEXIS 23453 (D. N.J. Mar. 24, 1998).
  - Gonzalez v. Guinther 1998 October 23 (Box 56)
  - Grabner v. John Alden Life Ins. Co. 1998 May 12 (Box 56)
  - Grissom v. Blackwell 1998 August 24 (Box 56)
  - Guibilo v. United States 1998 June 18 (Box 56)
  - Guzman v. Baltimore Life 1998 October 27 (Box 56)
  - Holy Name Friary v. Borough of East Rutherford 1998 April 21 (Box 56)
    HIV/AIDS
  - Int'l Longshoreman's Ass'n, Local 1478-2 v. Hudson Refrigerating Co. 1998 November 02 (Box 56)
  - Ipcja v. McDonough 1998 March 10 (Box 56)
  - Jackson v. Pinchak 1998 April 06 (Box 56)
  - Kato v. Nat'l R.R. Passenger Corp. 1998 March 24 (Box 56)
  - Kierstead v. Suter 1998 January 08 (Box 56)
    Opinion; Order; Exhibit A; Opinion; Order (1998 March 10)
  - Kim v. New England Mut. Life Ins. Co. 1998 August 11 (Box 56)
  - Kocses v. Home Depot 1998 May 28 (Box 56)
    Opinion; Order; Opinion; Order (1998 July 30)
  - In re Larkin 1998 May 22 (Box 56)
  - Larosiliere v. Morton 1998 November 13 (Box 56)
  - List v. Morton 1998 September 30 (Box 56)
  - Lodato v. United States 1998 January 06 (Box 57)
    Military readiness
    Subversive activities
  - Mann v. U.S. Postal Serv. 1998 June 15 (Box 57)
  - Miles v. United States 1998 January 28 (Box 57)
  - Morales v. Morton 1998 April 13 (Box 57)
  - Morgran Stiftung v. AmEuro Capital Corp. 1998 October 23 (Box 57)
  - Muhammad v. Green 1998 April 16 (Box 57)
  - Mujahid v. Morton 1998 March 24 (Box 57)
    Opinion; Order; Opinion; Order (1998 August 10)
  - Murphy v. Port Auth. 1998 October 15 (Box 57)
  - Navieras NPR v. AZ Carriers 1998 June 26 (Box 57)
  - N.J. State Council of Carpenters v. Bay Ridge Constr. 1998 February 20 (Box 57)
    Opinion; Order; Exhibit 1
  - N.J. Turnpike Auth. v. PPG Indus. 1998 May 15 (Box 57)
    N.J. Turnpike Auth. v. PPG Indus., 16 F. Supp. 2d 460 (D. N.J. 1998).
  - Noire v. Givaudan-Roure Corp. 1998 February 02 (Box 57)
    Research and development
  - Old Bridge Owners Coop. Corp. v. Twp. of Old Bridge 1998 August 07 (Box 57)
  - O'Neal v. Pinchak 1998 July 10 (Box 57)
  - Osteotech v. Gensci Regeneration Sci. 1998 May 04 (Box 57)
    Opinion; Order; Order Amending Opinion (1998 May 27)
    Osteotech v. Gensci Regeneration Sci., 6 F. Supp. 2d 349 (D. N.J. 1998).
  - Owen v. WWOR-TV 1998 March 20 (Box 57)
  - Padillo v. Apfel 1998 August 26 (Box 57)
  - Paramount Aviation Corp. v. Agusta 1999 June 26 (Box 57)
    Opinion; Order; Opinion; Order (1998 July 22)
  - P.C. Help Serv. v. Graham 1998 July 13 (Box 57)
  - Pearce v. Invisible Fence Co. 1998 March 17 (Box 57)
    Opinion; Order; Opinion; Order (1998 May 15)
  - Peavy v. Brown 1998 May 19 (Box 57)
  - Perez v. Citicorp Individual Banking Group 1998 March 03 (Box 58)
    Opinion; Order; Opinion; Order (1998 November 09)
  - Perez v. United States 1998 September 30 (Box 58)
  - Perry v. County of Monmouth 1998 July 06 (Box 58)
    Health promotion and preventive care
  - Philadelphia Produce Credit Bureau v. Jersey Produce Co. 1998 February 04 (Box 58)
    Opinion; Order Granting Motion to Set Intervention Bar Date; Exhibit A; Exhibit B; Letter-Opinion (1998 March 10); Order Grantin Motion to Allow Use of PACA Trustee's Tin Number Without PACA Escrow Account (1998 March 10)
  - Pirone v. Nw. Mut. Life Ins. Co. 1998 May 12 (Box 58)
  - Pitino v. Great Atl. & Pac. Tea Co. 1998 October 02 (Box 58)
  - Pollan v. Genisys Reservation Sys. 1998 June 04 (Box 58)
    Opinion; Order; Opinion; Order (1998 July 06)
  - Product Possibilities v. Ferraro Foods 1998 July 06 (Box 58)
  - Rosatelli v. United Capital Corp. 1998 March 23 (Box 58)
  - Russ Berrie & Co. v. N. Am. Bear Co. 1998 February 18 (Box 58)
  - Rycoline Prod. v. C&W Unlimited 1998 March 31 (Box 58)
    Opinion; Order; Opinion; Order (1998 August 26)
  - Ryder Truck Rental v. Metro Mailing Sys. 1998 May 29 (Box 58)
  - Sabrin v. Moran 1998 February 03 (Box 58)
    Opinion; Order Granting Plaintiffs' Motion for Attorneys' Fees; Order (1998 February 06); Stipulation of Dismissal; Consent Order
  - Sarullo v. U.S. Postal Serv. 1998 April 02 (Box 58)
  - Scarfi v. Secon Metals Corp. 1998 April 24 (Box 58)
    Opinion; Order; Opinion; Order (1998 July 30); Amended Order for Judgment (1998 July 31)
  - Seeward v. Frieder 1998 November 06 (Box 58)
    Opinion; Order Granting Middletown Dump Inc. Reasonable Attorney Fees
  - Solucorp Indus. v. Tristate Restoration Co. 1998 October 09 (Box 58)
  - Sorokko v. Nippon Life Ins. Co. of Am. 1998 June 02 (Box 58)
  - Status Int'l v. M&D Mar. 1998 January 15 (Box 58)
    Opinion; Order; Opinion; Order (1998 April 24)
  - Storm v. Twp. of Woodbridge 1998 March 23 (Box 58)
  - Storm v. Young 1998 August 20 (Box 58)
    Opinion; Order; Opinion; Order (1998 November 05); Opinion; Order (1998 November 23)
  - Tagliarine v. Comm'r 1998 July 22 (Box 58)
  - Tarczynski v. Barbo 1998 July 06 (Box 58)
  - In re Tavares 1998 March 13 (Box 58)
  - Thompson v. Corestates Fin. Corp. 1998 January 12 (Box 58)
  - Twp. of West Orange v. Whitman 1998 April 29 (Box 59)
    Twp. of West Orange v. Whitman, 8 F. Supp. 2d 408 (1998).
  - Trian Group v. Accident & Cas. Ins. Co. of Winterthur 1998 August 12 (Box 59)
  - Tyger v. Magarino 1998 June 23 (Box 59)
  - Tyndell v. E. Jersey State Prison 1998 January 12 (Box 59)
  - United States v. Home Builders Inst. 1998 May 12 (Box 59)
  - United States v. One 1993 Porsche 968 Cabriolet Auto. 1998 July 08 (Box 59)
  - U.S. Small Bus. Admin. v. Chang 1998 April 30 (Box 59)
  - Valderrama v. United States 1998 March 30 (Box 59)
  - Ward v. N.J. Natural Gas Co. 1998 December 15 (Box 59)
  - Westley v. Morton 1998 August 13 (Box 59)
  - Williams v. Apfel 1998 October 29 (Box 59)
  - Williams v. Morton 1998 January 13 (Box 59)
  - Williams v. Nickolopoulos 1998 May 04 (Box 59)
- Papers, 1999 (Box 59-63)
  All papers dated 1999.
  - Aduna-Yap v. Nordstrom 1999 January 21 (Box 59)
  - Aiello v. Union County 1999 March 09 (Box 59)
  - Alston v. Williams 1999 November 18 (Box 59)
  - Antonio B. v. Jersey City Bd. of Ed. 1999 September 23 (Box 59)
  - Aziz v. Dep't of Corr. 1999 December 03 (Box 59)
  - Bayside Cas. Ins. Co. v. United States 1999 June 11 (Box 59)
  - Berdiel v. Apfel 1999 February 22 (Box 59)
  - Besas v. Reno 1999 March 19 (Box 59)
  - In re Bey 1999 September 20 (Box 59)
  - Borough of Bogota v. CSX Corp. 1999 November 30 (Box 59)
  - Brewer v. Epstein & Sons 1999 December 14 (Box 59)
  - Brisar Indus. v. C.B. Displays 1999 December 30 (Box 59)
  - Brown v. Barbo 1999 June 03 (Box 59)
  - Brown v. Int'l Bhd. of Elec. Workers 1999 May 11 (Box 59)
    Opinion; Order; Amended Opinion (1999 May 17)
  - Bunch v. All Pro Sports & Entm't 1999 April 19 (Box 59)
    Opinion; Order; Opinion; Order (1999 July 15)
  - Callaway Golf Co. v. Fairway to Heaven 1999 July 30 (Box 60)
  - Centennial Ins. Co. v. Lithotech Sales 1999 December 13 (Box 60)
  - Ctr. for Hope Hospice v. Sec'y of Health & Human Serv. 1999 January 06 (Box 60)
    Medicare
  - Chambers v. Pitts 1999 June 11 (Box 60)
  - Clayton v. PetSmart Store Support Group 1999 January 08 (Box 60)
  - Conte, Inc. v. Kawasaki Kisen Kaisha, Ltd. 1999 December 13 (Box 60)
  - Dadic v. Wuest 1999 January 22 (Box 60)
  - Daniels v. Thomas & Betts Corp. 1999 April 28 (Box 60)
  - Doege v. Shalala 1999 May 25 (Box 60)
    Home and outpatient care
  - DeNofa v. DeNofa 1999 March 23 (Box 60)
    Opinion; Order Ι Opinion; Order (1999 April 12)
  - Dy-Core of Pa. v. Rothe-Johnson Project Serv. Corp. 1999 April 06 (Box 60)
  - EDGAR Online v. Parisi 1999 December 07 (Box 60)
    Internet and video services
  - Enriquez v. Morton 1999 August 31 (Box 60)
  - Equal Employment Opportunity Comm'n v. Shelcore 1999 June 30 (Box 60)
  - Eubank v. Portside Apartments Urban Renewal Co. 1999 May 18 (Box 60)
  - Farquharson v. Immigration & Naturalization Serv. 1999 January 06 (Box 60)
  - Fed. Home Loan Mortgage Corp. v. Moye 1999 August 16 (Box 60)
  - Fed. Ins. Co. v. Hock 1999 January 21 (Box 60)
  - Fernandez v. United Parcel Serv. 1999 April 30 (Box 60)
  - Fiore v. Pharmacia & Upjohn Co. 1999 July 20 (Box 60)
    Opinion; Order │ Opinion; Order (2000 July 12)
  - George v. Am. Bioproducts 1999 April 05 (Box 60)
    Opinion; Order │ Opinion; Order (20000225 )
  - Georgen v. Desert Health Prod. 1999 August 17 (Box 60)
  - Grinblat v. Benel 1999 April 14 (Box 60)
    Opinion; Order │ Opinion; Order (2000 November 22)
  - Hardy v. United States 1999 January 29 (Box 60)
  - Harrow v. Prudential Ins. Co. of Am. 1999 December 23 (Box 61)
    Harrow v. Prudential Ins. Co. of Am., 76 F. Supp. 2d 558 (D. N.J. 1999).
  - Harte v. Int'l House of Pancakes 1999 December 28 (Box 61)
  - Hellriegel v. Zucker-Zarett 1999 February 24 (Box 61)
  - Hernandez v. Comm'r 1999 September 23 (Box 61)
    Opinion; Order; Opinion; Order (1999 November 11)
  - Imperial Spirits v. Trans Marine Int'l Corp. 1999 February 17 (Box 61)
    Kazakhstan
    Imperial Spirits v. Trans Marine Int'l Corp., No. 98-5469, 1999 U.S. Dist. LEXIS 9586 (D. N.J. Feb. 17, 1999).
  - Indemax v. Nordson Corp. 1999 June 15 (Box 61)
  - Jones v. N.J. Transit Rail 1999 August 20 (Box 61)
  - J.P. v. E. Brunswick Twp. Bd. of Ed. 1999 April 07 (Box 61)
  - Knowledge Commc'n Serv. v. AIU N. Am. 1999 August 20 (Box 61)
  - Lagg v. Amtrak 1999 April 28 (Box 61)
  - Larkin v. Beneficial N.J., Inc. 1999 February 11 (Box 61)
  - Leon v. Comm'r 1999 July 23 (Box 61)
  - Loria v. Lockwood Boat Works 1999 April 30 (Box 61)
  - Mansol Assoc. v. Mansol Indus. 1999 April 22 (Box 61)
  - Mardini v. Viking Freight 1999 December 02 (Box 61)
    Mardini v. Viking Freight, 92 F. Supp. 2d 378 (D. N.J. 1999).
  - Marlow v. DeFusco 1999 December 16 (Box 61)
  - Martelli v. N.J. State Dep't of Corr. 1999 November 18 (Box 61)
    Opinion; Order of Partial Dismissal
  - Matos v. Comm'r 1999 June 25 (Box 61)
  - Medina v. Barbo 1999 July 09 (Box 61)
  - Mery v. N.J. Dep't of Ed. 1999 May 04 (Box 61)
  - Miller v. Morton 1999 December 10 (Box 61)
  - Mitchell v. Apfel 1999 March 04 (Box 61)
  - Morris v. Barbo 1999 August 23 (Box 62)
  - Morzh Oy Ab v. Express Shipping Serv. 1999 September 27 (Box 62)
    Finland
  - Mullen v. Port Auth. 1999 December 17 (Box 62)
    Mullen v. Port Auth., 100 F. Supp. 2d 249 (D. N.J. 1999).
  - Murphy v. Port Auth. 1999 March 01 (Box 62)
  - McDonnell v. N.J. Transit Rail Operations 1999 March 09 (Box 62)
  - McKinnie v. Super. Ct. 1999 June 09 (Box 62)
  - Nat'l Sea Prod. v. LaGalia 1999 July 26 (Box 62)
  - Nelson v. Comm'r 1999 July 09 (Box 62)
  - N.J. Payphone Ass'n v. City of East Orange 1999 December 13 (Box 62)
    Telecommunication rates and fees
  - In re N.J. Secretarial Sch. 1999 November 18 (Box 62)
  - Nwachukwu v. AFD Contract Furniture 1999 December 29 (Box 62)
  - Okoro v. United States 1999 December 08 (Box 62)
  - Payne v. Union County 1999 March 22 (Box 62)
  - Perez v. Citicorp Individual Banking Group 1999 October 27 (Box 62)
  - Plummer v. United States 1999 December 29 (Box 62)
  - Precise Exercise Equip. v. Cybex Int'l 1999 January 08 (Box 62)
    Physical fitness and lifestyle
  - Radowitz v. Equitable Life Assurance Soc'y 1999 November 29 (Box 62)
  - Riel v. Meadowlands Ctr. for the Arts 1999 March 02 (Box 62)
  - Rivera v. Cont'l Airlines 1999 July 16 (Box 62)
  - Rojas v. United States 1999 July 09 (Box 62)
  - Rycoline Products v. C&W Unlimited 1999 December 28 (Box 62)
  - Semeraro v. AGL Welding Supply Co. 1999 May 03 (Box 62)
  - Sharma v. United States 1999 January 06 (Box 62)
  - Sheth v. Edison Twp. 1999 May 25 (Box 62)
  - Shuart v. Guhl 1999 August 10 (Box 63)
  - Siss v. County of Passaic 1999 May 19 (Box 63)
    Siss v. County of Passaic, 75 F. Supp. 2d 325 (D. N.J. 1999).
  - Smith v. Essex County Dep't of Health & Rehab. 1999 January 05 (Box 63)
  - Smith v. Essex County Jail 1999 January 19 (Box 63)
  - Snyder v. Am. Ass'n of Blood Banks 1999 February 24 (Box 63)
  - Sotelo v. United States 1999 April 28 (Box 63)
  - Storm v. Young 1999 January 20 (Box 63)
  - Swinton v. Foley 1999 October 15 (Box 63)
  - Szalkowski v. Roy F. Weston, Inc. 1999 February 22 (Box 63)
  - Thompson v. Corestates Fin. Corp. 1999 January 08 (Box 63)
  - In re Top Grade Sausage 1999 April 16 (Box 63)
    In re Top Grade Sausage, No. 99-393, 1999 U.S. Dist. LEXIS 16529 (D. N.J. Apr. 16, 1999).
  - United Stationers Supply Co. v. Rod 1999 February 22 (Box 63)
  - Util. & Transp. Contractors Ass'n of N.J. v. Essex County Improvement Auth. 1999 May 20 (Box 63)
    Opinion; Order; Exhibit I
  - Valladolid v. Comm'r 1999 December 16 (Box 63)
  - Vandever v. Alpert 1999 October 26 (Box 63)
  - Villanueva v. Comm'r 1999 December 30 (Box 63)
  - Visual Tel. Int'l v. Pickens 1999 August 26 (Box 63)
  - Williams v. McKeen 1999 March 03 (Box 63)
  - Williams Envtl. Serv. v. Akzo Nobel Chem. 1999 June 09 (Box 63)
  - Winstead v. State 1999 March 12 (Box 63)
  - Wright v. J.M. Huber Corp. 1999 July 28 (Box 63)
  - Young v. City of New Brunswick 1999 April 23 (Box 63)
- Papers, 2000 (Box 64-67)
  All papers dated 2000.
  - Aburomi v. Englehardt 2000 October 31 (Box 64)
  - Alamo v. Cobb 2000 May 19 (Box 64)
  - Ali v. Johnson 2000 July 10 (Box 64)
  - Almonte v. United States 2000 May 24 (Box 64)
  - Angelica Textile Serv. v. Cathedral Healthcare Sys. 2000 June 01 (Box 64)
  - Assoc. Commercial Corp. v. Sarco Int'l 2000 May 26 (Box 64)
  - Avendano v. Apfel 2000 August 04 (Box 64)
  - Barnes v. Kerr 2000 November 22 (Box 64)
  - Battle v. Blackwell 2000 August 28 (Box 64)
  - Benjamin v. Inchcape Shipping Serv. 2000 June 16 (Box 64)
  - Bd. of Tr. v. Centra 2000 June 30 (Box 64)
    Tennessee
  - Bostic v. N.J. Ins. Underwriting Ass'n 2000 August 21 (Box 64)
  - Buck v. Twp. of Neptune 2000 September 28 (Box 64)
  - Buglino v. Comm'r 2000 May 01 (Box 64)
  - Canfield Scientific v. Cambridge 2000 October 12 (Box 64)
  - Colangelo v. Port Auth. 2000 December 28 (Box 64)
  - County of Morris v. Nationalist Movement 2000 August 08 (Box 64)
  - Crossroads Cogeneration Corp. v. Orange & Rockland Util. 2000 August 17 (Box 64)
  - Cruz v. Apfel 2000 July 31 (Box 64)
  - D'Alessandro v. Hendricks 2000 June 29 (Box 64)
  - Daniels v. Thomas & Betts Corp. 2000 May 30 (Box 64)
  - Day v. Bambo 2000 May 02 (Box 64)
  - D.B. Consolidated Enter. v. Walgreen Co. 2000 February 25 (Box 64)
    Opinion; Order; Opinion; Order (2000 October 19)
  - Doege v. Shalala 2000 July 31 (Box 64)
  - Doherty v. Teamsters Pension Trust Fund 2000 November 14 (Box 64)
  - Duran v. Mellon Mortgage Co. 2000 May 16 (Box 64)
    Opinion; Order; Opinion; Order (2000 July 13)